Guide to the Targ Editions Archive, 1953-1994 (Bulk 1979-1985) MSS.149
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series XIX: Wallace Shawn, Our Late Night, Targ Editions No. 21
  - Bound manuscript: Four Meals In May, Shawn, Our Late Night, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 135)
  - Bound manuscript: Aunt Dan and Lemon, Shawn, Our Late Night, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 136)
  - Sample title page, Shawn, Our Late Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 137)
  - Colophon samples, Shawn, Our Late Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 138)
  - Unbound signature, Shawn, Our Late Night, undated (Box 6, Folder 139)
  - Prints and clippings, Shawn, Our Late Night, 1975-1986 (Box 6, Folder 140)
- Series XX: Norman Mailer, The Last Night, Targ Editions No. 22
  Correspondence, production materials, and press related to the publication of Norman Mailer's story The Last Night by Targ Editions.
  - Correspondence, Mailer, The Last Night, 1977-1983 (Box 7, Folder 141)
  - Financial records, Mailer, The Last Night, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 142)
  - Orders, Mailer, The Last Night, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 143)
  - Original story, Mailer, The Last Night, 1962 (Box 7, Folder 144)
  - Sample title page, paper sample with title page measurements, Mailer, The Last Night, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 145)
  - Unbound signatures, Mailer, The Last Night, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 146)
  - Unbound signatures with Targ correction, Mailer, The Last Night, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 147)
  - Press clippings, Mailer, The Last Night, 1983-1984 (Box 7, Folder 148)
- Series XXI: Eleanor Sullivan, Whodunit: A Biblio-Bio-Anecdotal Memoir of Frederic Dannay, Targ Editions No. 23
  Correspondence, production materials, and press related to the publication of Eleanor Sullivan's Whodunit by Targ Editions.
  - Correspondence, Sullivan, Dannay, Whodunit, 1979-1991 (Box 7, Folder 149)
  - Financial correspondence, Sullivan, Whodunit, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 150)
  - Orders, Sullivan, Whodunit, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 151)
  - Manuscript fragments, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 152)
  - Paper sample, sample title page, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 153)
  - Ellery Queen sketches, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 154)
  - Photographs, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 155)
  - Clippings and bibliographies, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 156)
  - Miscellaneous clippings, Sullivan, Whodunit, undated (Box 7, Folder 157)
  - A Silver Anniversary Tribute to Ellery Queen, Sullivan, Whodunit, 1954 (Box 7, Folder 158)
- Series XXII: William Targ, Abacus Now: Footnotes to Indecent Pleasures and Observations on Fine Book Printing, Book-Collecting and Matters Personal including How to Survive in the Computer Age, Targ Editions No. 24
  Correspondence and production materials related to the publication of William Targ's Abacus Now by Targ Editions.
  - Correspondence, Targ, Abacus Now, 1983-1988 (Box 7, Folder 159)
  - Financial records, Targ, Abacus Now, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 160)
  - Orders, Targ, Abacus Now, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 161)
  - Writings, essays, and revisions, Targ, Abacus Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 162)
  - Unbound signatures with corrections, Targ, Abacus Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 163)
  - Unbound signatures and plates, Targ, Abacus Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 164)
  - Paper, color, and type samples, Targ, Abacus Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 165)
  - Proof with sample paper and boards, Targ, Abacus Now, undated (Box 7, Folder 166)
- Series XXIII: M. F. K. Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, Targ Editions No. 25
  Correspondence, production materials, and press related to the publication of M. F. K. Fisher's Spirits of the Valley by Targ Editions.
  - Correspondence, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, 1985-1987 (Box 7, Folder 167)
  - Financial records, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 168)
  - Orders, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 169)
  - Unbound signatures, colophon sample, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 170)
  - Paper samples, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, undated (Box 7, Folder 171)
  - Press clippings, Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, 1984-1985 (Box 7, Folder 172)
- Series XXIV: Gabriel Garcia Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, unpublished
  Correspondence and production materials related to the preparation of Gabriel Garcia Márquez's The Solitude of Latin America for publication by Targ Editions.
  - Correspondence, Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, 1983-1990 (Box 7, Folder 173)
  - Financial records, Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 174)
  - Orders, Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, 1983 (Box 7, Folder 175)
  - Manuscript and sample title page, Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, 1982, 1984 (Box 7, Folder 176)
- Oversize - Series I-XXIV
  Oversize correspondence, production materials, and press related to the publication of various Targ Editions volumes.
  - Proof with corrections, Henry Roth, Nature's First Green, Targ Editions No. 1, February 15, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 177)
  - New York Times Book Review clipping, inscribed by John Updike, Three Illuminations..., Targ Editions No. 2, June 20, 1993 (Box 8, Folder 178)
  - Complete proof and assorted fragments, John Updike, Three Illuminations..., Targ Editions No. 2, March 21, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 179)
  - Complete proof and assorted fragments with corrections, Ray Bradbury, Beyond 1984, Targ Editions No. 3, April 16,1979 (Box 8, Folder 180)
  - Proof fragments, proof, and original lecture, Saul Bellow, "Nobel Speech", Targ Editions No. 4, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 181)
  - Proof of title page with revisions, and sample boards, Kate Millett, Elegy For Sita, Targ Editions No. 5, 1979 (Box 8, Folder 182)
  - Board sample, Laura Riding, Discription of Life, Targ Editions No. 8, undated (Box 8, Folder 183)
  - Proofs with corrections, John Updike, Ego and Art in Walt Whitman, Targ Editions No. 10, undated (Box 8, Folder 184)
  - Proofs with revisions and correction, John Updike, Hawthorne's Creed, Targ Editions No. 12, April 23, 1981 (Box 8, Folder 185)
  - Proofs with corrections and letter from Diane Wakoski, Saturn's Rings, Targ Editions No. 14, February 2, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 186)
  - Corrected proof, final proof, D.R. Bensen, Edward Gorey,Irene, Good-Night, Targ Editions No. 15, March 2, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 187)
  - Proofs with corrections and comments, Marguerite Yourcenar, The Alms of Alcippe, Targ Editions No. 16, undated (Box 9, Folder 188)
  - Proof with corrections, original woodcut, Antonio Frasconi, Theodore De Vinne, The First Editor: Aldus Pius Manutius, Targ Editions No. 17, 1982 (Box 9, Folder 189)
  - Proof fragments with corrections, James A. Michener Collectors, Forgers..., Targ Editions No. 19, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 190)
  - Proof, W.D. Snodgrass, The Four Seasons, Targ Editions No. 20, undated (Box 9, Folder 191)
  - Print of still from performance, proof of colophon with corrections, Wallace Shawn, Our Late Night, Targ Editions No. 21, undated (Box 9, Folder 192)
  - Two proofs with corrections, Norman Mailer, The Last Night, Targ Editions No. 22, December 30, 1983 (Box 9, Folder 193)
  - Assorted proof pages and illustrations, William Targ, Abacus Now, Targ Editions No. 24, undated (Box 9, Folder 194)
  - Proofs with corrections, M.F.K. Fisher, Spirits of the Valley, Targ Editions No. 25, 1985 (Box 9, Folder 195)
  - Proof sheets, Gabriel Garcia Márquez, The Solitude of Latin America, unpublished, 1984 (Box 9, Folder 196)
- Series XXVI: William Targ, Secret Lives, 1983-03
  - Secret Lives Manuscript, 1983-03 (Box 10, Folder 1-4)